{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1019","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #90","address":"19190 Kelly Rd","owner":"Little Caesars Enterprises, In","licenseNumber":"035073","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-82.96443,42.41964","geojson":{"id":"1019","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.964431705,42.4196404800001]},"properties":{"name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #90","owner":"Little Caesars Enterprises, In","address":"19190 Kelly Rd","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035073","establishmentid":"1019","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/12/2016"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3309","name":"Wendy's Old Fashioned Hamburgers","address":"19100 Kelly Rd"},{"establishmentid":"4097","name":"Subway","address":"11435 Kelly Road"},{"establishmentid":"1734","name":"Empire Lounge","address":"15000 Houston-Whittier"},{"establishmentid":"4888","name":"Chung's","address":"12518 Kelly Rd"},{"establishmentid":"841","name":"Denby High School","address":"12800 Kelly Rd"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44132","inspectionDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"5-403.12","violationDescription":"Condensate drainage and other nonSEWAGE liquids and rainwater shall be drained from point of discharge to disposal according to LAW.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Liquid waste(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not drained from point of discharge","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Drain from point of discharge to proper disposal system."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"40222","inspectionDate":"2017-10-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in soiled, wet conditions","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM (POTS/PANS)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."}]},{"inspectionid":"44179","inspectionDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in soiled, wet conditions","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM (POTS/PANS)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."}]},{"inspectionid":"36370","inspectionDate":"2016-09-01T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1019"}}